ANZHELIKA MAKSUMOVA

Phone: +48 572 120 332

Email: likamax93@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/angelica-maks

umova-9b665315a/



Objective

Project Manager

Summary

- 4-year experience in IT project management (outsourcing, internal products, support)
- Practical experience of working with Agile methodologies (Scrum, Kanban, Scrumban)
- 2 years of company process improvement and PM lead experience
- Skilled in creation and support of the company working guidelines, business process optimization

Skills

English Proficiency: Upper Intermediate+

Tools: JIRA, Confluence, YouTrack, Trello; Google Meet, Slack, Teams, Zoom; Figma, Miro;

BrowserStack, Testflight

Key skills: mobile and web projects management (Scrum, Kanban, Scrumban), product MVP planning from presale to delivery, company process optimization, knowledge base for dev and PM department, PM mentoring, interviewing, team management, scope-time-cost control, assistance in mobile and web apps testing

Education

Sep 2018 - Dec 2018 - Educational Center of HTP "IT-Academy"

Course: Business Analysis

Description: Accredited Course in Business Analysis in the Software Development Field

Sep 2010 - Jul 2014 - College of Linguistics and Humanities (Minsk State Linguistic

University Affiliate)

Specialization: Linguistics, Document Support of Management

Work experience

Aug 2021 - Oct 2023

Project manager, Head of PMO at Solvelt (Warsaw, Poland)

Main responsibilities: mobile and web apps project management (Scrum, Scrumban), internal product MVP management, project management process guideline, company processes optimization, PM mentoring, interviewing, company knowledge base, resource management, dev department metrics and reporting

Domains: e-commerce, health&fitness, social networks, live streaming, productivity

Clients: Sweden, USA, UAE, CIS

Oct 2020 - Apr 2021

Project Manager at Dashbouquet Development (Minsk, Belarus) Main responsibilities:

Web apps project management (Scrum, Kanban): direct communication to clients, requirements analysis and clarification, planning, team management, scope-time-cost control, demo for clients, project documentation, team motivation, retrospectives. Active participation in company work process optimization.

Domains: e-commerce, recruiting, education, logistics, event management and live streaming Clients: Great Britain, Israel, Germany, Saudi Arabia

Mar 2019 - Aug 2020

IT projects support & management at RichBrains (Minsk, Belarus) Main responsibilities:

Support and management of web projects (Kanban, Scrum): direct communication with clients, requirements elicitation and analysis, project documentation, dev team management, sprints planning, manual testing, clients and users support

Domains: e-commerce, education, health&fitness

Clients: Great Britain, USA, CIS

Feb 2018 - Feb 2019

Office Support, Executive Personal Assistant at HQSoftware (Minsk, Belarus) Main responsibilities:

Company offices support, office budget planning and reporting, documentation support, CEO personal assistant

Sep 2016 - Jan 2018

Product Implementation Assistant, Administrative Manager at Trizeri Co., Ltd. (Phuket, Thailand)

Main responsibilities:

Product development assistance (proofreading, preparing user guides, texts for a landing page, automated emails; manual testing); business process elicitation, system setup for potential client, staff training, user experience collecting and analysis; administrative management (office support, documentation, budget, staffing).